ruggable.com 2015-12-20

# Kitchen Rugs Washable - Large Area Rugs | Privacy Policy

PLEASE NOTE that our privacy policy has changed, effective January 1, 2015.

Product Bliss, LLC and its affiliates (collectively, “us”, “our” or “we”), own and operate the RUGGABLE® 2-peice rug system brand.  Product Bliss collects customer information to help us to serve you better. We respect your privacy and are committed to maintaining and using this information responsibly. This privacy policy addresses the use and disclosure of personal information we collect from you. By visiting our website, or providing your information to us, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy.

**Personal information we collect about you**

Any personal information you provide to us is maintained on secure servers and our internal systems. We collect personal information when you sign up online or create or update your account, log-in, place an order, communicate online using our contact us form, sign up to receive our newsletters, shop online, participate in a sweepstakes, contest, promotion or survey, or join our social networking sites. This information we collect may include, but is not limited to, your contact information (for example, your name, email address, billing and shipping addresses and phone number) and your credit card information.

**Non-personal information we collect about you**

Your web browser or client software may transmit certain geographic information or information regarding your computer (capabilities, browser, IP addresses, etc.) to us. We may use this information to help us understand who uses our website and to improve and market our website in general and to help us to improve the products and tools we offer online.  In addition, we may use such information for security, system integrity (the prevention of hacking, etc.), or enforcement purposes.

**How we use your information**

We use your personal information to complete your purchase transaction, to keep you informed about the status of your order, to identify your product preferences so we can notify you of new or additional products that might be of interest, to notify you of any important information concerning the product you purchased such as revised care or application instructions, disclaimers or product recalls, and for internal marketing, profiling, or demographic purposes, so we can adapt our products and services to better suit your needs. We may also use information about your product preferences and interests in order to improve our site design and enhance your shopping experience.  In the event of a sale of some or all of our business, Product Bliss may disclose your personal information to a purchaser that agrees to abide by the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. 

You should also be aware that we may disclose specific information about you if required to do so by law, governmental request, process or court order or based on our good faith belief that it is necessary to conform or comply with such law, request or court order or to protect the users of our websites or the public.

**Cookies and web beacons**

We currently use the services of a few carefully selected companies to help manage and optimize our Internet business and communications. These companies help us to measure the effectiveness of our advertising and better understand how visitors use our sites. To do this, cookies are placed on computer browsers and web beacons are placed on our websites on our behalf. The type of information collected in this manner includes pages visited, products viewed and products placed in your shopping cart. By supplementing our records, this information helps us to identify what pages are most attractive to our visitors, which of our products most interest our customers and what kinds of offers our customers like to see.

Cookies are small data files that are automatically stored on your computer when you visit our websites. Cookies are used to track the pages of the websites you’ve visited and do not retain any personally identifiable information such as your name, address or any financial information. We may use cookies to enable you to use certain website features, remember the items in your shopping cart, store your preferences, recognize you when you return to our website, track your orders, and monitor and maintain information about your use of our websites. By using our websites, you consent to our placement of cookies on your computer.

You may occasionally get cookies from our business partners or other third parties. We have no access to or control over these cookies.

Most internet browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you do not wish to have cookies on your system, you can set your browser preferences to refuse them or to alert you when cookies are being sent. In order to disable cookies, please consult your browser's "help" section for instructions. Additionally, if you have an Adobe Flash player installed on your computer, your Flash player can be set to reject or delete Flash cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the features of our websites.

Web beacons are small strings of code that are placed in a web page or in an email message. They are sometimes called "clear GIFs" (Graphics Interchange Format) or "pixel tags". Web beacons are most often used in conjunction with cookies to track activity on our websites. When you visit a particular web page, web beacons notify us of your visit. Since web beacons are used in combination with cookies, if you disable cookies the web beacons will only detect an anonymous website visit. When used in an email, Web beacons enable us to know whether you have received the email. ** **

**How we work with third party service providers**

Product Bliss works with reputable third parties who perform services on our behalf. Sometimes these service providers need information about our customers in order to do their jobs, such as to ship orders or to maintain and manage our customer database and report on customer behavior and/or preferences. We will attempt to ensure that these entities do not use your personal information for any other purpose, and that they have agreed to maintain the confidentiality, security, and integrity of the personal information they obtain from us.

**Marketing email communications**

If you do not wish to receive Product Bliss marketing emails or promotions, you may opt out by clicking on the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of all Product Bliss marketing emails, or you may email [contactus@ruggable.com](mailto:contactus@ruggable.com) with “remove” in the subject line. Be sure to send the email from the address you want removed. Please be aware that it can take up to 10 business days to remove you from our marketing email lists.

**Links to other sites**

To enhance your shopping experience, our websites may include links to other sites outside our family of brands. Those websites will have their own privacy policies that you may wish to review. Product Bliss has no responsibility for these linked websites.

**Privacy of young children**

Product Bliss is concerned about the privacy of young children and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from a child under 13. We do not sell products for purchase by children and all children's products we sell are for purchase by adults only.

**Security**

The security of your information is very important to us. When ordering online from our website, your information is protected by Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. SSL technology encrypts your order information to protect it from being decoded by anyone other than Product Bliss.

While we implement these and other security measures on our sites, please note that 100% security is not always possible. You play a role in protecting your information as well. Because your password permits access to your personal information, please keep your password secret and do not disclose it to others.

**Accessing our web sites from outside the U.S.**

We do not currently accept international orders, but if you are visiting Ruggable.com from a location outside of the United States, you will be connected through and to servers located within the United States. You may use the contact us link on the homepage to email or call us to get assistance with an international order. By providing your information to us, you agree that all personal information will be used in accordance with this privacy policy and pursuant to U.S. law. ** **

**Your California rights**

Product Bliss collects various types of personal information about you both online and offline, as described in this privacy policy. Under California law, customers of Product Bliss who are residents of California may request certain information about our disclosure of personal information during the prior calendar year to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to us at the following address: Ruggable, 2 Piece Rug System Customer Relations 832 Coastal Beach Road, Henderson, NV 89002.  Alternatively, you may send us an email at [contactus@ruggable.com](mailto:contactus@ruggable.com) with the words "California Privacy Rights" in the subject line.

**Privacy policy updates  **

We may update our privacy policy from time to time. Whenever we make a change, we will post the updated policy at this site and we encourage you to check our policy periodically. If we make a material change to our privacy policy that would lessen your privacy rights, we will either continue to honor our prior policy for information that we collected when it was in force, or we will ask for your consent to the change. If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please contact us:

  * By email:  [contactus@ruggable.com](mailto:contactus@jcrew.com)
  * By phone: 877-RUGGABLE (877-784-4225)
  * By mail:    Ruggable, 2 Piece Rug System Customer Relations, 832 Coastal Beach Road, Henderson, NV 89002

Effective as of January 1, 2015.
